Guide to the George D. Vaill, Associate Secretary, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1919-1988; Accession 1990-A-009
  - UNIVERSITY ADMINISTRATIVE AFFAIRS AND PERSONAL MEMORABILIA
    - Duke University: Correspondence Regarding Loan of Yale Mace to Duke Art Gallry, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 340)
    - University of th West Indies: University Singers, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 341)
    - Windham College: Inauguration of President, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 342)
    - Florida Colleges Correspondence, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 343)
    - New England Council, 1959-1972 (Box 28, Folder 344)
    - The New England Renaissance Conference, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 345)
    - The New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (NEACSS), 1965 (Box 28, Folder 346)
    - United Nations Association: International Cooperation Year (ICY), 1965 (Box 28, Folder 347)
    - Amphibious Assault, 1968 July 23 (Box 28, Folder 348)
    - President Giamatti's Inauguration, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 349)
    - Kingman Brewster's Inauguration, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 350)
    - Kingman Brewster's Retirement, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 351)
    - Yale-in-China, 1967-1977 (Box 28, Folder 353)
    - Yale-in-China, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 354)
    - Guest Book, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 355)
    - Guest Book, 1935-1968 (Box 29, Folder 356)
    - Guest Book (See Box 32, Folder 5), 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 357)
    - Album Presented to George Vaill by the Chinese Opera Society of New Asia College (See "Yale-in-China" Box 28, Folders 45, 46), 1956 (Box 29, Folder 358)
    - Nathan Hale First Day Stamp (See Also Box 32, Folder 6), 1977 October 14 (Box 29, Folder 359)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly: Notes on Articles of interest to George Vaill, undated (Box 29, Folder 360)
    - Berkeley College: "Ode to Dorothy's Boy", 1975 (Box 29, Folder 361)
    - Branford College
      - 1963, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 362)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 363)
      - Minutes of Meetings of the Fellows of Branford College, 1942-1948 (Box 29, Folder 364)
      - Minutes of Meetings of the Fellows of Branford College, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 365)
      - Miscellaneous Material Regarding Branford Fellows, including Correspondence Regarding Something for Blair (SFB) Project, 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 366)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1971 (Box 29, Folder 367)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1968 (Box 30, Folder 368)
      - Miscellaneous: Includes Correspondence with Master William Zinsser, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 369)
      - Branford College Press, 1956-1966 (Box 30, Folder 370)
      - Branford Tower Bulletin, 1940-1948 (Box 30, Folder 371)
    - Davenport College: Record of the Fellows, Volume II, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 372)
    - Jonathan Edwards College, 1971, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 373)
    - Morse College, 1963, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 374)
    - Pierson College, 1970, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 375)
    - Saybrook College, 1957, 1972, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 376)
    - Saybrook College Pendants, Crests and Miscellany, undated (Box 30, Folder 377)
    - Silliman College (Box 30)
    - Miscellany, 1940-1947 (Box 30, Folder 378)
    - Salamanders, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 379 - 380)
    - Inscriptions, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1940 (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1940 (Box 31, Folder 383 - 385)
    - Stiles College, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 386)
    - Timothy Dwight College, 1962-1973 (Box 31, Folder 387)
    - Trumbull College, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 388)
    - Vaill's Donation of his Body to Medical School, 1960-1975 (Box 31, Folder 389)
    - The Choate School: Correspondence regarding George D. Vaill's Son, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 390)
    - George D. Vaill: Personal Material, 1946-1950 (Box 31, Folder 391)
    - Poems and Commemorations, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 392)
    - George D. Vaill: Miscellaneous Family Correspondence, 1927-1969 (Box 31, Folder 393)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 394 - 403)
  - OVERSIZE MATERIAL
    - Removal of Nathan Hale Statue from Pedestal at Connecticut Hall, 1969, June 14 (Box 32, Folder 404)
    - Printing Samples [See Box 19], 1950 (Box 32, Folder 405)
    - Photograph of Andover Class of 1982 at 150th Celebration [See Box 21], 1928 (Box 32, Folder 406)
    - Engravings of Andover Buildings [See Box 21], undated (Box 32, Folder 407)
    - Guest Book [See Box 29], 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 408)
    - Nathan Hale U.S. Postal Card presented to the University See Box 29], 1977 October 14 (Box 32, Folder 409)